{
    "subject": "resource/Gabriella_Wilde",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1989-04-08",
    "human_readable": "Gabriella Wilde was born on April 8, 1989.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8940591216087341,
            "question": "When was Gabriella Wilde born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6399165987968445,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde's ethnicity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.610217273235321,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5950397849082947,
            "question": "Where did Gabriella Wilde grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801784992218018,
            "question": "What is Gabriella Wilde's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5145015120506287,
            "question": "In what year did Gabriella Wilde begin her acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4392533004283905,
            "question": "Is Gabriella Wilde involved in any philanthropic work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34339848160743713,
            "question": "What are some of Gabriella Wilde's notable film roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33563920855522156,
            "question": "What are some of Gabriella Wilde's interests outside of acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33383867144584656,
            "question": "Has Gabriella Wilde won any awards for her acting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gabriella Wilde was born on April 8, 1989.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4595_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Gabriella Wilde's interests outside of acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4595_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Gabriella Wilde's notable film roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4595_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Gabriella Wilde involved in any philanthropic work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4595_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4595_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Gabriella Wilde was born on 8 April 1989, which supports the statement \"Gabriella Wilde was born on April 8, 1989.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}